Good afternoon everyone and welcome to FinTech Plus Sync's second quarter 2023
earnings call. I'm John Doe, CEO of FinTech Plus. We've had a stellar Q2 with a
revenue of 125 million, a 25% increase year over year. Our gross profit margin
stands at a solid 58% due in part to cost efficiencies gained from our scalable
business model. Our EBITDA has surged to 37.5 million translating to a
remarkable 30% EBITDA margin. Our net income for the quarter rose to 16
million which is a noteworthy increase from 10 million in Q2 2022. Our total
addressable market has grown substantially thanks to the expansion of
our high yield savings product line and the new robo advisor platform. We've been
diversifying our asset backed securities portfolio investing heavily in
collateralized debt obligations and residential mortgage backed securities.
We've also invested 25 million in AAA rated corporate bonds enhancing our risk
adjusted returns. As for our balance sheet total assets reached 1.5 billion
with total liabilities at 900 million leaving us with a solid equity base of
600 million. Our debt to equity ratio stands at 1.5, a healthy figure considering our
expansionary phase. We continue to see substantial organic user growth with
customer acquisition cost dropping by 15% and lifetime value growing by 25%.
Our LTV CAC ratio is at an impressive 3.5 x.
In terms of risk management we have a value at risk model in place with a 99%
confidence level indicating that our maximum loss will not exceed 5 million in the next
trading day. We've adopted a conservative approach to managing our leverage and have
a healthy tier one capital ratio of 12.5%. Our forecast for the coming quarter is
positive. We expect revenue to be around 135 million and 8% quarter over quarter
growth driven primarily by our cutting edge blockchain chain solutions and AI
driven predictive analytics. We're also excited about the upcoming IPO of our
fintech subsidiary pay plus which we expect to raise 200 million significantly
bolstering our liquidity and paving the way for aggressive growth strategies. We
thank our shareholders for their continued faith in us and we look forward to an even
more successful Q3. Thank you so much.